Guilherme Patriota

Software Engineer and Data Science Teacher



APT 1001-6800 Chemin de la Côte-St-Luc Montréal/QC



+1 (438) 926-0872



linkedin.com/in/guilhermepatriota



guipatriota@gmail.com

About me -

Guilherme Patriota is an IT Professor and Electrical Engineer with a Masters in AI in search of an opportunity to work in his areas of interest in Montreal. Working as a University Professor in the Software Engineering and Data Science courses at UNINTER - International University Center, in Brasil, since 2021 and as Professor in other universities since 2016.

Skills

Teaching

AWS, Linux, Docker

Eletronics, IoT, MQTT, Kafka

C++, R, Skala

Python, Pandas, Tensorflow, AI, Logic

3D Modeling, 3D Printing

SQL, NoSQL

Big Data, Hadoop, Spark

(*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

[Interests]

High technologies; Data Analysis; Big Data; Teaching

Education

2013-2016	MBA in Healthcare Improuvments into medical equipments maintenance.	FGV/Brazil
2009-2011	M.Sc. Electrical Engineer AI with electronics and telecommunications.	UFPR/Brazil
2002-2006	B.Sc. Electrical Engineer Electronics and telecommunications.	UFPR/Brazil
2004-2004	B.Sc. Electrical Engineer Sandwitch degree in Electrical Engineer - Electronics	ENSPS/France

Complementary Studies

2020	Knowledge discovery in database and datamining. UFPR/Brazil	60h
2020	Data Science foundations. Aldeia Coworking/Brazil	32h
2020	Introduction to computer programming using python. MITx	9 weeks
2020	AI fundamentals. Data Science Academy	8h
2020	Datascience 2.0. Data Science Academy	8h

Experience

since 2016	University Professor	FAESP and UNINTER
	University Professor in the Software Engineering,	Computer Engineer-
	ing and Data Science courses at UNINTER - Int	ernational University
	Center in Brasil.	

New Technologies Developer	Boa Impressão 3D
Develop eletronics and software for new 3d	printers and other prod-
ucts. Manage the assembly line.	
	Develop eletronics and software for new 3d

2018-2020	3D Printer Technician.		GS3D
	Build, repair end configure 3d printer and make and prin	t 3d	modeling
	spare parts.		

2012-2018	Medical Equipments Engineer.				Several Hospitals in Br			oitals in Brazil
	Maintain	and	repair	medical	equipments	and	manage	technician
	teams.							

Other information

Disponibility

OWP until November 2023. Part or full time.

Languages

English, French and Portuguese.

Social

GitHub github.com/guipatriota

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/guilhermepatriota